inviteads.com 2014-06-23

# End User Privacy Policy | inviteAds

The company providing the platforms and services for: inviteAds and Adk2, (together the “Company” or us), their respective websites (the “Websites”) and the services and technologies they provide (each, the “Services”) has a strong commitment to protect the privacy of its users. Our privacy policy (the “Policy”) aims to ensure the protection of privacy of our users and to provide them with control over the decision how their information is being used.

**Acceptance of Terms**

By using or visiting the Websites, you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Websites or Services. The Privacy Policy should read together with the Terms of Use and Copyright Policy which together comprise of the full agreement between the Company and its users.

**What this Policy Covers**

This policy covers “end-users” or Internet users, as opposed to our clients or subscribers. Our business enables advertisers to provide you with advertisements that are relevant to your interests and therefore, more useful to you. This Privacy Policy explains how we treat your privacy, so you may decide whether to benefit from our Platform, including how you may opt-out. This policy does not cover the practices of companies that we does not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage, including any cookies placed from outside our services.

**Information Collection and Cookies**

To help companies personalize the advertisements you see to enhance ad effectiveness and relevancy, improve our services, create new products, conduct research, and provide reporting for internal and external clients, we are required to use standard tracking technologies, such as cookies, local shared objects, and pixel tags to collect information about the way in which users may respond to, select and interact with an ad or any content provided therein, analyze usage patterns and record your browsing activity. Cookies are little bits of text that are set and accessed from within a browser on your computer. They are accessed to collect and send statistical information when a user returns to a website or goes to another website. Local shared objects (also known as “LSOs” or “Flash cookies”) are used by the authors of files that are read by Adobe Flash Player and the websites hosting those files in a similar manner as cookies, but can also be used for a variety of purposes such as keeping track of information you provided and remembering your preferences. To learn how to reject or delete LSOs, click [here ](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/flash-player.html "here")for the Adobe Flash Player privacy policy. Pixel tags (also known as “web beacons” or “clear GIFs”) are often used in combination with cookies, and is a type of technology placed on a website for the purpose of tracking activity. We only use these tracking technologies to better target and analyze consumer behavior with the goal of enabling our clients to provide better and more relevant advertisements. We do not use them to alter your Internet experience, other than to show you a targeted ad.

WE DO NOT USE COOKIES OR ANY OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES TO PROCESS OR COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU. For purposes of this document, personally identifying information (PII) is information that personally identifies you and that is not otherwise publicly available, such as your first and last name, social security or identification number, credit card number, phone number, or email address. We use tracking technology for non-PII only, which is information that cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity, such as your computer’s configuration, and the version and type of browser you are using. While some non-PII could be used in conjunction with other information to personally identify a user (e.g., the address of a web page or of a computer on the Internet could identify a user when combined with Internet service provider records), we ourselves generally have no way of tying any of the information we collect back to a particular user, and in the unusual circumstance that we could use an Internet protocol address for such purposes, we do not do so unless required by law.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We do not rent or sell any information about you to others, or trade any such information. We may share aggregate information, and other non-PII information about you for various purposes, such as to perform or enhance our services. We may also share any information (including to personally identify a user) with our affiliates or service providers, in response to any request by authorities that we believe legally compels us to respond, to establish or exercise legal rights or defend against legal claims, to investigate, prevent, or take action for violations of our terms of service, or as otherwise required by law, or to transfer such information, subject to the terms of this Policy, if we were to acquire, or were acquired by or merged with, another company.

**International Data Transfer** [NOTE: please review the below]

We transfer your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy to the United States, where it is processed, collected and stored using Amazon Web Services, Inc., (“AWS”) a subsidiary of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates. The AWS Customer Agreement can be found [here](http://aws.amazon.com/agreement/ "here"). We take adequate measures to ensure the privacy of data subjects, and except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not transfer your data to any other person, whether in the United States or in another country.

**Your Ability to Edit/Delete Your Information**

Because we do not collect PII, and the information we obtain is automatic through tracking technologies, we cannot provide you the ability to edit or update your non-PII information after it is collected. You can always opt-out though. If you opt-out from tracking technologies, any information that we already have collected or stored may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request, but in no event longer than a year. This may be the case even though no more information remains in our active databases.

**Privacy Opt-Out**

You may further opt-out of providing information to us and through of our collection of non-PII from cookies placed on your computer, by clicking on the following URL: <http://ads.adk2.com/opt-out>. By clicking on this opt-out link, we will no longer collect non-PII information from your website or users (from the domain adk2.com). You may opt back in, by clicking on the following URL: <http://ads.adk2.com/opt-in>.

**Children**

Our products and services are not designed for, or directed at children. We do not create segments to specifically target anyone under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any information from them. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a child under the age of 13, we will take all appropriate steps to delete such information from our records.

**Data Security and Retention**

We have industry-standard physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to make sure information is collected, processed and shared only in accordance with this Policy. Once you uninstall or opt-out, all tracking technologies, including cookies, will expire within 2 days. No security measures, however thorough, are perfect and there can be no absolute assurance of security. Therefore, we cannot and do not offer an absolute guarantee or warrant the security of the information we possess.

**Contact Us with Questions or Concerns**

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@inviteAds.com.

**Updates to this policy**

From time to time we may make changes to this Policy and publish the same prominently on our website with the date of last update. These changes will supersede any prior changes. You understand and agree that we will treat your continued use of our product or services after such changes have been published as your acceptance of the updated Policy.

**Disclaimer Regarding Linked Sites**

While using the Services you may be linked from or to third parties sites. We are not be responsible for information, content, terms, offers or any other use of privacy policy at these sites. When you use a link to go from our Website or Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. By your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on the Website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Last Update: June 2013**
